Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away.
We're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop
it We will be one, go ahead
year he and his crew
made it to the waters of
the new world he's on
the fast track to infamy
absolutely brutal
absolutely crazy he roasted
pirates on a skewer and
filmed it for the world
to see he opened fire
on innocent civilians
for no good reason recently
ranked number one in
the most annoying pirates
who should just go
away competition the
irrepressible irredeemable
Bartolomeo!
You're going on a one-way trip!
Straight to hell!
All of you!
You can't talk to people like that!
I don't see you right now!
Whoa!
Hey, wait!
What are you about to do?
Huh?
Is that a...
It's a ball!
You gotta get out of here!
Move it, old man! You're too slow!
Get out of my way!
Step aside, Slowpoke!
Ladies first, remember?
I'll give you all of my money!
Just help me!
A ball?
Pathetic.
Not too popular with the crowd, are you?
Who cares?
They're jackasses anyway.
Fine, let's move on.
Anyway, forget that, bastard.
Block B has just one
final competitor left.
This fighter is loyal
to our king, Doflamingo.
So loyal, in fact, that he brought the king
a giant gold pillar from a distant land.
He's more than worthy of
winning this tournament.
He's here!
He's been ransacking
towns in various countries
whose people slathered
our nation's great name.
Stakes are already high today,
but for him, they're even higher
as the Bullet of Dressrosa.
And at long last, he's been granted this
opportunity by King Doflamingo himself!
The infirmaries down the hall—we're
low on stretchers, so walk if you can.
These dudes are a mess.
The champ really got them! Hey,
nice
getter—but do
you think I'm blind?
I don't care how good the
disguise is when it comes to
the guy who managed to swerve
my career into the skids.
I'm gonna
know his face.
his face
It's you?
You're a jerk.
You really messed up that
poor chestnut head guy.
Right?
It's Bellamy.
Yeah, Lamby!
But wait, what are you doing here?
What do you care?
It's not like I'm glued
to Chaya, you know.
I can go wherever I please.
Besides, Doe Flamingo
is a real hero of mine.
I've been a fan ever since I was a kid.
I don't care about the flame flame fruit.
But I still have plenty to gain
by busting some heads out there.
I'll take you down as
many times as I need you.
I'll warn you, I'm not
the same man as before.
For starters, I saw the
Sky Island just like you.
I lost all of my crewmates on that trip.
but it turned my view of the
whole damn world upside down.
What happened up there?
You didn't hurt anyone, did you?
Maybe.
Anyway, I'm not going to hold
a grudge against you anymore.
There's a big wave that's about
to crash through this world,
and I think the Doflamingo
ship can ride it out.
Either way, I'm done.
The stakes are already high today,
but for him they're even higher
if he's able to achieve victory.
Then this dedicated
combatant will be promoted to
an executive position in
the Don Quixote family.
This pirate is a strong
contender; he could take it all.
Give it a four!
Bellamy the Hyena!
Bellamy! Bellamy! Bellamy! Bellamy!
He's a local, but surely
he's not that great.
Morons.
It looks like all 138 competitors
have gathered in the ring!
I hope you're all ready
Now, who wants to be first?
What the bunch of cheaters!
Hey, wait—that's not fair!
They can't team up.
Battle royale means every man
for himself! You're cowards.
Get
your name calling out of the way now!
You won't be saying much
when we're done with you.
There
can only be one winner!
And it's sure as hell not
gonna be you, Bartolomeo!
I
don't believe this!
It looks like several of our competitors
have decided to fight together!
together
That's loud?
It isn't good sportsmanship, but I suppose
it's not technically against the rules.
And I bet I know who came
up with that plan, too?
Well, the kingdom of Prodence
is tactician, Dogamo.
Come on!
We're taking the flame flame fruit back
to Prodence with us, no matter the cost.
Our ruler, Elisabello II, was always
destined to be a weapon of devastation.
He boasts a superhuman
physique that he can
level any opponent with
a single deadly punch.
He once obliterated an entire
enemy fort with one blow,
creating panic all over the land.
But there is one drawback to his power.
It takes a full hour of
concentration to build
up the energy for just
one of those punches.
Rumor has it, that punch could even take
down the four emperors if it hit them,
but he could only use it once per fight.
So whether he wins or loses
all depends on his timing.
It's a one-of-a-kind attack.
They call the king punch
Your majesty, it's time
I'm not ready yet.
You'll have to keep guarding me
Understood.
This is a chance for all
of you to earn your keep.
Protect his majesty and eliminate
as many challenges as you dare!
Are you all right with this, LaPont? Huh?
Dressrosa's army captain helping
a tactician from another country?
Money toss.
That's just the world we live in, Bellamy.
I'm here to make some quick cash,
not chase after some pipe dream,
which means your time's up. Oh, really?
You sure about that? Yeah!
They fell out of the ring.
They're out. Who's next?
Anyone who falls into the moat
won't be coming back to join us,
thanks to the Coliseum's
most unique attraction.
The little fighting fish.
It's out of the frying
pan and into the fire.
That's the famous Corrida Coliseum
for you, ladies and gentlemen.
You fall, and then you say goodbye.
How difficult, huh?
Now, spring!
Deathknotch!
All right, Abdullah!
Edorstein!
You shouldn't have turned
your back to me. Huh?
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha!
Dirty cowards! Huh?
Cowards, huh?
No, we're opportunists.
Go back to the water
where you belong, freak!
Huh, so what made you think you could
participate in a human competition anyway?
Come on, why don't you say something back?
I pity you, huh, don't think I got that.
Let your fists do the talking—oh,
that sounds like a great idea!
idea
4 ,000 wrist fists.
As Jinbei once told me,
my friend and hope of our people,
we must find a way to create
good relations with fists.
Thus, I shall continue
fighting to the end.
It appears Blue Gilly has decided to
start attacking Elisabello II's entourage.
Ow, ow, ow.
Damn that blue-haired bastard.
What the hell's wrong with you?
How could you lose to some
spindly unarmed nobody? It...
it doesn't really matter how
spindly this unarmed freak is!
Why not come closer?
It's no fun when you're so far away.
You're not shy, are you?
This guy's from the Longleg tribe,
so attack his legs, numbskulls!
Damn!
His movements are unpredictable!
I can't read them at all! Hew! Hew! Hew!
That's three more down!
And Bluegilly has done it again by
quite literally kicking some ass!
Hey, who's that gladiator
in the Skull Cape?
Just take a look over there.
He's a real powerhouse.
You recognize him?
You got a point.
In all the years I've been fighting
here, I've never seen him before.
Every gladiator from the Coliseum is
trained to fight, both a sword and a shield.
But he uses just a blade, like
a samurai from the Wano Kingdom.
him let's test his
skill i'm game too
slow you see that gladiator the one
in the cape with the blue skull yeah
quite the experienced fighter rather
odd that he's new here i thought the
same at first but i've got this feeling
like i've seen him somewhere a man
like that who fought without a shield.
Why can't I remember his name?
What's he doing?
Hey, move it, you'll get killed!
Why isn't anybody attacking him?
Is this all a joke to him?
Apparently he's one of those
insufferable newcomers,
the same as that Straw Hat Luffy.
I'll be sure to teach
him a lesson as well.
What are those things, Cabbage?
Posters to locate members
of the worst generation.
But I need some fresh copies now.
The knife marks make it hard to see.
Hey, this is dumb, okay?
Just let it go.
Not till I kill them.
I can't.
Since the prize for this competition
is so desirable, I was hoping Apu,
or Kid, or at least one
of them would enter.
But I'm not even sure
I'd know if I saw them.
Who knows?
Any of them could have concealed
their faces the way Burgess did.
And what if I do see them?
Do I wait for them to
move on to the next round?
Pardon me.
Is it all right if I watch
the fight with you gentlemen?
Hmm, we have a good view
of the fight from here.
How's old Garp doing these days?
Tell me, Luffy.
Hey, you mean you know my grandpa? You!
Know him? Sure.
Years ago, he nearly killed me.
And now I carry that grudge against him,
his children, and his grandchildren.
You